export const chapter = "Chapter - 4: THE ANIMAL KINGDOM ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "What are the two main groups in which animals can be classified based on their living habits?",
          optionA: "Big and small",
          optionB: "Wild and domestic",
          optionC: "Fierce and pleasing",
          correctAnswer: "Wild and domestic",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is a wild animal that lives in dens or lairs?",
          optionA: "Horses",
          optionB: "Bears",
          optionC: "Cows",
          correctAnswer: "Bears",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Where do elephants, zebras, deer, and giraffes live among wild animals?",
          optionA: "Dens",
          optionB: "Under the trees",
          optionC: "On trees",
          correctAnswer: "Under the trees",
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following animals is an omnivore?",
          optionA: "Lions",
          optionB: "Cows",
          optionC: "Bears",
          correctAnswer: "Bears",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the term for animals that are tamed and kept for their usefulness?",
          optionA: "Fierce animals",
          optionB: "Wild animals",
          optionC: "Domestic animals",
          correctAnswer: "Domestic animals",
        },
        {
          question: "Where are cows typically kept among domestic animals?",
          optionA: "Stable",
          optionB: "Shed",
          optionC: "Kennel",
          correctAnswer: "Shed",
        },
        {
          question: "What do animals like lions, tigers, and crocodiles eat?",
          optionA: "Plants",
          optionB: "The flesh of other animals",
          optionC: "Both plants and flesh of other animals",
          correctAnswer: "The flesh of other animals",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Where do rats and snakes typically live among the wild animals mentioned?",
          optionA: "Dens",
          optionB: "Under the trees",
          optionC: "Holes",
          correctAnswer: "Holes",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the term for animals that eat only plants and are known as herbivores?",
          optionA: "Lions",
          optionB: "Elephants",
          optionC: "Bears",
          correctAnswer: "Elephants",
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following animals is an omnivore?",
          optionA: "Lions",
          optionB: "Cows",
          optionC: "Bears",
          correctAnswer: "Bears",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Wild animals that live in the wild or in forests are called ___________.",
          optionA: "Tamed animals",
          optionB: "Domestic animals",
          optionC: "Wild animals",
          correctAnswer: "Wild animals",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Most of the wild animals live in natural shelters like in dens, on the trees, or under the trees while some make their ___________.",
          optionA: "Cages",
          optionB: "Hives",
          optionC: "Homes",
          correctAnswer: "Homes",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Elephants, zebras, deer, giraffes, etc. live under the ___________.",
          optionA: "Caves",
          optionB: "Skies",
          optionC: "Trees",
          correctAnswer: "Trees",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Domestic animals are kept in different types of houses made by ___________.",
          optionA: "Nature",
          optionB: "Humans",
          optionC: "Animals",
          correctAnswer: "Humans",
        },
        {
          question: "Horses are kept in a ___________.",
          optionA: "Coop",
          optionB: "Kennel",
          optionC: "Stable",
          correctAnswer: "Stable",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Animals like lions, tigers, crocodiles, etc. eat the ___________ of other animals.",
          optionA: "Plants",
          optionB: "Flesh",
          optionC: "Insects",
          correctAnswer: "Flesh",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Animals like bears, crows, monkeys, etc. eat both plants and ___________ of other animals.",
          optionA: "Insects",
          optionB: "Flesh",
          optionC: "Seeds",
          correctAnswer: "Flesh",
        },
        {
          question: "Rats and snakes live in ___________.",
          optionA: "Dens",
          optionB: "Holes",
          optionC: "Caves",
          correctAnswer: "Holes",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Animals like elephants, goats, cows, etc. eat only ___________. These are called herbivores.",
          optionA: "Meat",
          optionB: "Plants",
          optionC: "Insects",
          correctAnswer: "Plants",
        },
        {
          question: "Different animals eat different types of ___________.",
          optionA: "Water",
          optionB: "Food",
          optionC: "Air",
          correctAnswer: "Food",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Wild animals live in natural shelters like dens, on trees, or under trees.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Most domestic animals are kept in natural shelters like dens or lairs.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Elephants, zebras, deer, and giraffes live in dens or lairs.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Rats and snakes live in holes.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Cows, goats, horses, and hens are considered domestic animals.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Cows are usually kept in kennels.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Animals like bears, crows, and monkeys are herbivores.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Groundwater is obtained by drilling into the ground.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Animals like lions, tigers, and crocodiles eat only plants.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Different animals eat the same types of food.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
